Guide to the New York University Stern School of Business Collection of Pig Memorabilia MC.234
New York University Archives
- Series III: Utilitarian Objects
  - Subseries III K: Jewelry Containers
    - Sow Washing Piglet, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 10)
      White sow washing piglet over basin with a scrub brush; ceramic
    - Drum with Pig Container, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 5)
      Robin-egg blue drum container with blue pig on top; ceramic
    - Pig by Flower Container, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 16)
      Pink, ceramic pig by large white flower with green leaves
    - Pigs with Floral Trough, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 17)
      Three, pink, ceramic pigs eating from a floral trough
    - Pig in Floral Clown Costume, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 18)
      Ceramic container in the shape of a pig in floral clown costume; tape residue
    - Pig Near Stump, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 4)
      Beige, ceramic pig with burgundy detail near tree stump
    - Pig and Green Top Hat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 23)
      Pink pig leaning on oversize, green top hat; ceramic
    - Pig by Bucket and Basket, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 19)
      Light brown, ceramic pig by green bucket and brown basket
    - Pigs and Package, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 7)
      One pink pig on top of the green and orange package and the other peering through the package; ceramic
    - Pig Sleeping on Tray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 16)
      Pink pig sleeping on green tray; ceramic
    - Pig Driving Tractor, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 17)
      Pink pig driving tractor; ceramic
    - Pig by Large Shoe, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 18)
      Pink pig next to large, green shoe; ceramic
    - Pigs Eating from Trough, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 1)
      Two pink, ceramic pigs eating from a green and gold trough that reads "Souvenir of Boston, Mass".
    - Pigs in Front of Top Hat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 6)
      Two pink pigs in front of a large, green top hat
    - Warthog Jewelry Tray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 8)
      Metal, warthog jewelry tray
    - Blue, Purple, and White Pig Container, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 20)
      Large, ceramic, blue, purple, and white pig container; tape taking off paint
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 25)
      Pink, ceramic pig with black spots holder; remnants of sponge in the holder
    - Jewelry Tray with Clear Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 5)
      White, ceramic tray with clear pig
    - Pigs in Basket, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 13)
      Pink pig peering through and another pig hanging over a white basket with gold accents; ceramic
  - Subseries III L: Mixed Objects
    This subseries of mixed objects contains buckets, candleholders, puzzles, measuring tapes, and pencil and paint brush holders with pigs decorating these items.
    - Pig with Large Head and Bow, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 26)
      White, ceramic pig with oversize head and bow; possibly a diffuser
    - Pigs with Telephone Holder, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 11)
      Two pink pigs in front of a large, gold, orange, and green telephone booth
    - Blue, Floral Pig Holder, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 18)
      Ceramic, blue, floral pig possibly meant to hold and store paint brushes or pencils
    - Pink Pig Thermometer, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 10)
      Pink, metal pig thermometer
    - Pig with Pearl Eyes, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 35)
      Plastic, gold, pig shaped measuring tape with pearl eyes and pearls on its back
    - Blue Pig with Red Hat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 13)
      Measuring tape in the shape of a robin-egg blue, plastic pig with red hat; text across back reads "This Little Piggy Comes from Waco, Texas"
    - Wooden Puzzle, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 5)
      Wooden, three-part, pig puzzle
    - Brown Pig with Closed Eyes, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 33)
      Brown, ceramic pig candle holder with closed eyes and red, yellow, and white spots
    - Bucket with Pig Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 3)
      Metal bucket depicting pigs engaging in human-like behaviors; signs of rust